hi my name is Chris Haggerty I work in
嗨，我叫克里斯·哈格蒂（Chris Haggerty），我在这里工作
the Java platform group at Oracle and
Oracle的Java平台小组和
today I'm gonna be talking about the
今天我要谈论的是
road to the Java 11 HTTP client in this
Java 11 HTTP客户端之路
session were going to be answering three
会议将要回答三个
questions why are we adding a new HTTP
问题，为什么我们要添加一个新的HTTP
client how long does it take and what is
客户需要多长时间以及什么
the role that development look like and
发展的角色以及
what are the benefits at you as an
作为您，您有什么好处？
application developer can get from the
应用程序开发人员可以从
new HTTP client in Java 11 enhancements
Java 11中的新HTTP客户端增强功能
to JDK are done through jdk enhancement
JDK是通过jdk增强完成的
proposals jeff's
杰夫的建议
Djebbour 10 is one of the first stop
杰布堡10号车站是第一站
publishing on the HTTP client and it is
在HTTP客户端上发布，它是
useful to look at the motivation section
有用的动机部分
in this gem it contains a number of
在这个宝石中，它包含许多
points discussing the URL connection API
讨论URL连接API的要点
which is the current API for performing
这是当前用于执行的API
HTTP exchanges URL connection was added
HTTP交流URL连接已添加
in JDK $1 back in 1996 and is protocol
在JDK $ 1上，是1996年的协议
agnostic it supports multiple protocols
不可知论它支持多种协议
like FTP mail to file access at one
像FTP邮件一样可以一次访问文件
point gopher as well as HTTP URL
点地鼠以及HTTP URL
connection in fact predates HTTP 1 1
实际上，连接早于HTTP 1 1
looking at the HTTP timeline we can see
查看HTTP时间轴，我们可以看到
that the RFC for HTTP 1 0 was published
HTTP 1 0的RFC已发布
in 1996 1:1 in 1999 and more recently
1996年为1：1，1999年为最近
HTTP 2 into 2015 there have been
HTTP 2进入2015年
countless bug fixes in the HTTP protocol
HTTP协议中的无数错误修复
implementation and numerous enhancements
实施和大量增强
such as larger than 2 gigabyte content
例如大于2 GB的内容
lengths and they expect 100 continue
长度，他们希望继续100
header to name but a few the
标头，但一些
implementation has reached its limit for
实施已达到极限
complexity after been around for more
经过更多的复杂性
than 20 years given that you are
超过20年，因为你是
connections protocol agnostic then it
然后与连接协议无关
can be a little cumbersome to use for
可能有点麻烦
HTTP since it suffers from restrictions
HTTP，因为它受到限制
of being a common protocol API while
成为通用协议API的同时
there is a concrete HTTP URL connection
有一个具体的HTTP URL连接
sub-type in many cases still just isn't
在许多情况下，子类型仍然不是
any natural place to document some of
任何自然的地方来记录一些
the HTTP specific behavior neural
HTTP特定行为神经
connection is based on java io streams
连接基于Java io流
which are inherently blocking this may
固有地阻止了这种情况
not have been such a limitation back in
并没有成为这样的限制
1996 but it is today treads are a
1996年，但今天是胎面
valuable costly resource and we don't
宝贵的昂贵资源，我们不会
want to unnecessarily tied them up
想要不必要地捆绑他们
especially waiting for data to be
特别是等待数据
received from the network looking again
从网络收到再次查看
at the HTTP timeline the HTTP to RFC was
在HTTP时间轴上，HTTP到RFC是
published in May 2015 the application
2015年5月发布了该应用程序
semantics of HDTV 2 are mainly the same
HDTV 2的语义基本相同
as that of HTTP 1 1 all the core
与HTTP 1 1一样，所有核心
concepts such as requests responses HTTP
请求，响应，HTTP等概念
methods status codes URI and headers are
方法状态代码URI和标头是
mainly the same instead HTTP 2 modifiers
主要与HTTP 2修饰符相同
how to data is formatted and transported
如何格式化和传输数据
between the client and server HTTP 2
客户端和服务器之间的HTTP 2
does however bring some new concepts
但是确实带来了一些新概念
that would have been very difficult or
那将是非常困难的，或者
almost impossible to model in the URL
几乎不可能在URL中建模
connection API like server push which
连接API，例如服务器推送
we'll take a look at later the HTTP 2
我们稍后会看一下HTTP 2
implementation is very different from
实现与
that of HTTP 1 1 defining a new HTTP
HTTP 1 1的定义新HTTP
client API for the Java SE platform is
Java SE平台的客户端API是
not easy especially if we expected to be
这并不容易，特别是如果我们期望
around for the next 20 years jack 110
在接下来的20年里，杰克110
was created in May 2014 almost exactly
几乎是2014年5月创建的
one year before the HTTP 2 or C was
在HTTP 2或C发布之前一年
published work actually began well
出版的工作实际上进展顺利
before the states in fact some of the
实际上在各州之前
early product types that went to several
早期的产品类型有几种
iterations were done around the Java 7
围绕Java 7进行了迭代
time frame in an open source project on
一个开源项目中的时间框架
the now-defunct java.net site which is
现在已经不存在的java.net网站
still available in the archives so this
仍可在档案中使用，因此
project has been worked on by several
该项目已经由几个人进行
engineers and spans over a number of
工程师和跨越许多
years Jeff content was integrated in JDK
年Jeff内容被集成到JDK中
9nj tk9 shipped in September 2017
9nj tk9于2017年9月发货
as you will know Java 9 brought a large
如您所知Java 9带来了
language change in the form of the
语言的变化形式
module system and the Java Runtime image
模块系统和Java运行时映像
is comprised at a set of modules
包含在一组模块中
alongside the module system a new
与模块系统一起，新的
concept of incubating features was added
孵化功能的概念已添加
we'll take a deeper look at incubating
我们将更深入地探讨孵化
features in the moment but for now all
目前的功能，但目前所有
we need to know is that the HTTP client
我们需要知道的是HTTP客户端
was added in jdk 9 as an incubating
是在jdk 9中添加的
feature a new incubator module named jdk
配备了一个新的孵化器模块，名为jdk
incubator HTTP client was added that
孵化器HTTP客户端添加了
module exports a single package jdk
模块导出单个包jdk
incubator HTTP that contains two
孵化器HTTP包含两个
complete HTTP api jeff 11 is an
完整的HTTP api jeff 11是
informational jet that describes what
描述什么的信息喷射
incubating features are their purpose
孵化功能是他们的目的
and their delivery mechanism through
及其传递机制
incubator modules
孵化器模块
simply put incubator modules are a means
简单地将孵化器模块放到一个位置
of putting non-final api's in the hands
将非最终api放在手中
of developers while the API is
API是
progressed towards finalization or
进行定稿或
removal in a future release incubating
在将来的版本中删除
an API is desirable as it allows the
API是可取的，因为它允许
standardization of an API to be deferred
API的标准化要推迟
for a short period of time the API is
在短时间内，API
still part of the JDK download so is
仍然是JDK下载的一部分，因此
available to the large number of Java
可供大量Java使用
developers the incubation time allows
开发人员的潜伏时间允许
for these developers to provide feedback
为这些开发人员提供反馈
on the API as well as the ability for
API的功能以及
the API to incorporate its feedback
API整合其反馈
before it is standardized an incubating
在标准化孵化之前
API is expected to be relatively
API预计会相对
short-lived in all cases it will be
在所有情况下都是短暂的
removed in a future release either
在将来的版本中删除
because it is standardized in which case
因为在这种情况下它是标准化的
its module and package name will change
其模块和软件包名称将更改
or if some fatal design flaw is
或者如果某些致命的设计缺陷是
discovered then it will be dropped
发现然后将其删除
looking at the HTTP client class from
从看HTTP客户端类
JDK Nayanar JDK 10 you will see that its
JDK Nayanar JDK 10您将看到它的
module and package name clearly
模块和软件包名称清楚
identified as being incubating there is
被确定为正在孵化
also a more scary-looking warning that
还有一个更可怕的警告
the API is an incubating feature and as
API是一个孵化功能，
such will be removed in a future release
此类将在以后的版本中删除
all this helps to notify the developer
所有这些都有助于通知开发人员
that if they are using this API then
如果他们正在使用此API，
they will need to take some action when
他们将需要采取一些行动，当
updating it to a future JDK release
将其更新到将来的JDK版本
incubator incubator modules are not
孵化器孵化器模块不是
resolved at compile time so an
在编译时解决，所以
additional command-line option needs to
其他命令行选项需要
be specified to tell the compiler to add
指定告诉编译器添加
the incubator module and make its types
孵化器模块及其类型
available here we are making the HTTP
在这里我们正在制作HTTP
client module available so the add
客户端模块可用，因此添加
modules command-line option is specified
指定了模块命令行选项
with the name of the HTTP client
HTTP客户端的名称
incubator module similarly incubator
孵化器模块类似的孵化器
modules are not resolved at runtime so
在运行时无法解析模块，因此
the add modules command-line option is
添加模块命令行选项是
heated again with the same value the
再次以相同的值加热
name of the HTTP client incubator module
HTTP客户端孵化器模块的名称
alternatively a modular application can
或者，模块化应用程序可以
include an explicit requires directive
包含一个明确的require指令
in its module info source file naming
在其模块信息源文件命名中
the HTTP client incubator module
HTTP客户端孵化器模块
regardless of how incubator modules are
不管孵化器模块如何
resolved either true explicit requires
解决了真正的显式要求
directives in the module info source
模块信息源中的指令
file or true commandlineoptions
文件或真正的命令行选项
a warning is emitted at both
双方都发出警告
compile-time and run-time to indicate
编译时和运行时指示
that an incubating feature is being used
正在使用孵化功能
the warning includes the name of the
警告中包括
particular incubating modules that are
特定的孵化模块
in use in this case just the incubating
在这种情况下使用只是孵化
HTTP client module has been used again
HTTP客户端模块已再次使用
this warning is intended to help notify
此警告旨在帮助通知
the developer that an incubating feature
开发人员具有孵化功能
is in use and that an action will need
正在使用中，需要采取措施
to be taken when updating to a future
更新到将来时要采取的措施
release so that's what we did in JDK 9
发布，这就是我们在JDK 9中所做的
JDK 10 the implementation was completely
JDK 10的实现是完全
overhauled to improve reliability and to
大修以提高可靠性并
make it more robust the API was also
使API更健壮
updated to incorporate the feedback that
更新以纳入反馈
was received on the incubating JDK 9
在孵化的JDK 9中收到
version 4 Java
Java 4版
a new JDK enhancement proposal was filed
提交了新的JDK增强建议
jeb 321 to standardize the API this
jeb 321来标准化API
required giving the HTTP client a
需要给HTTP客户端一个
standard module a package named davon F
标准模块名为davon F的软件包
HTTP this standard package now includes
这个标准包现在包含HTTP
the complete API and the incubating
完整的API和孵化
version has been completely removed any
版本已被完全删除任何
code that runs on JD k 9r JDK 10 and
在JD k 9r JDK 10和
uses the incubating API will need to be
使用孵化API将需要
updated at the very minimum the import
至少更新了导入
statements will need to be changed to
陈述将需要更改为
reflect a new package name and also any
反映新的软件包名称以及任何
module info source files that contain
包含以下信息的模块信息源文件
requires directives naming the HTTP
需要命名HTTP的指令
client incubator module will now need to
客户端孵化器模块现在需要
use the new standard module name
使用新的标准模块名称
similarly any command line options
类似地，任何命令行选项
specifying the incubating module name
指定培养模块名称
will need to be updated or may even not
将需要更新，甚至可能不需要更新
be necessary since all standard modules
有必要，因为所有标准模块
that are part of the Java SE platform
是Java SE平台的一部分
are resolved by default when running an
运行时默认解决
application on the class path let's take
类路径上的应用程序
a look at how to do that okay so here we
看看如何做到这一点，所以在这里我们
have a utility guest method it retrieves
有一个实用程序来宾方法检索
given your I and returns response body
给你我并返回响应主体
as a string first it creates a new HTTP
作为字符串，它首先创建一个新的HTTP
client over which the request will be
请求的客户
sent then it builds a new request with
发送，然后使用
the given URI then the send async method
给定的URI然后发送异步方法
is invoked to send a request and a body
被调用以发送请求和正文
handler a string factory method returns
字符串工厂方法返回的处理程序
a body hunger that converts the response
转换反应的身体饥饿
body bytes to a string the send async
正文字节发送到字符串发送异步
method returns a HTTP response of string
方法返回字符串的HTTP响应
that can be done chained up with the
可以与
then apply method from completable
然后从completable中应用方法
future to map the HTTP response of
将来映射的HTTP响应
string to its body type which is string
字符串为其主体类型，即字符串
in our case and a completable future of
就我们而言，以及
string is returned the main method
字符串返回的主要方法
simply calls get with the given URI and
只需使用给定的URI进行调用即可，
then join to block until the completed
然后加入阻止直到完成
the future completes
未来完成
then response body is printed out this
然后将响应主体打印出来
is using the incubating version of the
正在使用的孵化版本
API from JDK 9 so let's run that we can
JDK 9中的API，因此让我们运行
see the warning that an incubating
看到正在孵化的警告
module has been used and the name of the
模块已被使用，其名称
module and then the program executes
模块，然后程序执行
some princess response body is a string
一些公主反应身体是一个弦
which is just some XML there's also a
这只是一些XML，还有一个
modular version of the same code
相同代码的模块化版本
it's module info requires the JDK
它的模块信息需要JDK
incubator HTTP client module and exports
孵化器HTTP客户端模块和导出
a single package P that contains the
包含
code the code is almost identical the
代码代码几乎相同
previous code only prints ed modular
先前的代码仅打印ed模块化
tests so we know that this code is
测试，所以我们知道这段代码是
actually executing so let's run the
实际执行，让我们运行
configuration again with a warning from
再次发出警告
the compiler and from the runtime that
编译器以及运行时
incubating HTTP client has been used and
已使用孵化HTTP客户端，并且
again a response body is printed out so
再次打印出响应正文，这样
let's update this code for jdk 11 first
让我们先为jdk 11更新此代码
thing we do so we can update the STK
为此，我们可以更新STK
being used by the IDE and now we have a
被IDE使用，现在我们有了一个
lot of errors because the incubating API
许多错误，因为孵化API
is no longer present in JDK 11 so let's
不再存在于JDK 11中，所以让我们
update the import statements to reflect
更新导入语句以反映
the new standard package name which is
新的标准软件包名称是
Java net HTTP we can still see that
Java net HTTP我们仍然可以看到
there's red lines and this is because
有红线，这是因为
the require statement is not right so
require语句不正确，所以
let's update the module name there first
让我们先在那里更新模块名称
okay our import statements seem to be
好吧，我们的导入语句似乎是
accepted now
现在接受
oops the factory methods have been
哎呀，工厂方法已经
renamed in JDK 11 they are all prefixed
在JDK 11中重命名，它们都带有前缀
oops
哎呀
with love and they've moved to the body
有了爱，他们已经移到身体了
handlers class so body handlers have
handlers class，所以body handlers有
string so let's run that now and see
字符串，让我们现在运行它，看看
what happens okay we've got an error a
发生什么了好吧，我们有一个错误
compile time because the JDK Incubator
编译时间，因为JDK孵化器
HTTP client module is not found my IDE
在我的IDE中找不到HTTP客户端模块
is being configured in its preferences
在其首选项中配置
you add Incubator module it's a command
您添加孵化器模块，这是一个命令
line option so let's remove that you no
行选项，让我们删除您不
longer need that and run the modular
不再需要它并运行模块化
application again
再次申请
okay great it works this application
好的，它可以在此应用程序中工作
only uses the HTTP module so it only
仅使用HTTP模块，因此仅
needs to require Java net HTTP it could
需要使用Java net HTTP
of course have required Java SE which
当然需要Java SE
gives you the full job SC platform and
为您提供完整的SC平台，并
again that runs and prints out response
再次运行并打印出响应
body so let's update the non-modular
主体，所以让我们更新非模块化
application as well in the same way
同样的方式
again the factory methods have been
再次，工厂方法已经
moved and renamed so I just ruined a
移动并重命名，所以我毁了一个
configuration for the non modular
非模块化配置
application there's an application
有一个应用程序
running on the class pad and it again
在课本上运行，然后再次
mentions the fact that the incubator
提到孵化器的事实
module is not found so we need to edit
找不到模块，所以我们需要编辑
the configuration not this oops
这不是配置
edit the configuration and remove the
编辑配置并删除
explicit add modules that was used as a
显式添加模块，用作
runtime argument when were using JDK 9
使用JDK 9时的运行时参数
so that's let's run that again and it
因此，让我们再次运行它
works
作品
princess responds body so we've seen how
公主回应身体，所以我们已经看到了
to update a modular and non module
更新模块化和非模块化
application to update the import
应用程序更新导入
statements to reflect the new package
反映新包装的声明
name in jdk 11 as well as the new module
jdk 11以及新模块中的名称
name in the module info as well as some
模块信息中的名称以及一些
other minor changes around the renaming
重命名周围的其他细微变化
and moving of some of the factory
和一些工厂的搬迁
methods there are a number of benefits
方法有很多好处
that application developers can get from
应用程序开发人员可以从中获得
using the new HTTP client and we'll take
使用新的HTTP客户端，我们将采取
a look at the most significant of these
看看其中最重要的
over the next number of slides here are
在接下来的幻灯片数是
some of the goals that are listed in
列出的一些目标
Japan 10 support for HTTP 2 of course as
Japan 10对HTTP 2的支持当然是
well as HTTP 1 1 provide an asynchronous
和HTTP 1 1提供异步
API so as to get away from the blocking
API，以摆脱阻塞
semantics of the existing URL connection
现有URL连接的语义
use more modern language features like
使用更多现代语言功能，例如
generics and lambda as well as more
泛型和lambda以及更多
modern platform api is like completable
现代平台api就像是可完成的
future and the reactive streams
未来和反应流
interfaces additionally there is support
接口另外有支持
for the handling of the WebSocket
用于处理WebSocket
upgrade and a low-level web socket API
升级和低级Web套接字API
as I said earlier the application
正如我之前所说的
semantics of HTTP 2 are similar to that
HTTP 2的语义类似于
of HTTP 1 1
的HTTP 1 1
there are however significant
但是有重大意义
differences in how the two protocol
两种协议的差异
versions operate HTTP 2 uses just a
版本操作HTTP 2仅使用
single connection between the client and
客户端与
server which reduces the overhead of
服务器，减少了
setting up new connections
建立新的连接
for HTTP where the TLS handshake can
用于TLS握手可以进行的HTTP
take some time to complete this single
花一些时间来完成这首单曲
connection between the client and server
客户端和服务器之间的连接
can have multiple HTTP requests
可以有多个HTTP请求
multiplexed on it at the same time HTTP
同时在HTTP上多路复用
2 provides a new mechanism called server
2提供了一种称为服务器的新机制
push where a server upon receipt of a
将收到的邮件推送到服务器
request can if the if determines
如果可以，请求可以
appropriate issues syntactic requests to
适当的句法要求
the client resources that it believes
它认为的客户资源
the client will likely need along with
客户可能需要
the original request this can be used to
原始请求可以用来
speed up the retrieval of resources with
加快资源检索
a large number of embedded links the
大量的嵌入式链接
unwire format has been updated
取消连线格式已更新
significantly from data HTTP 1 1 HTTP 2
明显来自数据HTTP 1 1 HTTP 2
uses a more compact binary format and
使用更紧凑的二进制格式，
headers are compressed using H PAC
标头使用H PAC压缩
compression the HTTP client supports
压缩HTTP客户端支持
both HTTP 1 1 and HTTP 2 but prefers
同时使用HTTP 1 1和HTTP 2，但更喜欢
HTTP 2 by default for new clear non TLS
默认情况下，HTTP 2用于新的清除非TLS
connections the client automatically
自动连接客户端
adds the appropriate protocol of great
添加了合适的协议
headers to let us server know that the
标头，让我们的服务器知道
client supports HTTP 2 if the server
客户端支持HTTP 2（如果服务器）
also supports HTTP 2 then it can reply
也支持HTTP 2然后可以回复
as appropriate and the connection will
视情况而定，连接将
be upgraded for HTTP over TLS the client
客户端通过TLS通过HTTP升级
uses the application layer protocol
使用应用层协议
negotiation TLS extension to try to
协商TLS扩展以尝试
negotiate h2 with the server if the cert
如果证书与服务器协商h2
server supports H 2 then H 2 is used in
服务器支持H 2，然后将H 2用于
all cases if the server does not support
服务器不支持的所有情况
HTTP 2 then the connection falls back to
HTTP 2，然后连接回退到
HTTP 1 1 as of JDK 11 the TLS 1.3
从JDK 11 TLS 1.3开始的HTTP 1 1
protocol is supported the HTTP client
HTTP客户端支持该协议
leverages this and attempts to negotiate
利用这一点并尝试进行谈判
TLS 1.3 for all new TLS connections the
所有新的TLS连接的TLS 1.3
HTTP client supports an asynchronous
HTTP客户端支持异步
mode of operation request sent with the
与一起发送的操作模式请求
send async method return a compatible
发送异步方法返回兼容
future of HTTP response compatible
HTTP响应兼容的未来
future provides a number of methods for
未来提供了许多方法
building chains
建筑链
dependent actions that can be run either
可以运行的相关操作
synchronously or asynchronously in this
在此同步或异步
example same-day sync is given to
范例提供当日同步
request to be sent and also a body
请求发送，还有一个尸体
handler that converts the response body
转换响应主体的处理程序
bytes to a string the comparable future
字节到字符串可比较的未来
denne apply method maps to HTTP response
denne apply方法映射到HTTP响应
to its body type which in this case is a
它的身体类型，在这种情况下是
string the den accept method consumes
den accept方法消耗的字符串
the string and just prints it out
字符串，然后将其打印出来
finally the join method blocks until the
最后join方法阻塞，直到
response string is printed the HTTP
HTTP响应字符串
client follows the familiar Builder
客户遵循熟悉的生成器
pattern there are factories for creating
模式有工厂创建
builders for both the top-level HTTP
顶级HTTP的两个构建器
client and HTTP requests types in this
客户端和HTTP请求类型
example the HTTP client new builder
HTTP客户端新构建器示例
static factory method returns a new
静态工厂方法返回新的
builder of HTTP clients I connect
我连接的HTTP客户端的生成器
timeout for new connections is set to 20
新连接的超时设置为20
seconds and the client is built the HTTP
秒，客户端建立了HTTP
request has a similar new builder
请求具有类似的新生成器
factory then requests Uriah set a
然后工厂要求Uriah设置一个
request specific timeout a header
请求特定超时报头
indicating the content type since this
从此指示内容类型
will be a post request the body
将是职位要求的身体
publishers of file factory method is
文件工厂方法的发布者是
used to return a request body publisher
用于返回请求正文发布者
that publishes the content of the given
发布给定内容的
file path the request is then sent the
然后将请求发送到文件路径
Java platform provides the board for
Java平台为
reactive streams through a number of
通过许多反应性流
interfaces in a Java util concurrent
Java util并发中的接口
flow class there is a publisher for
流类有一个发布者
producing items a subscriber for
为订户生产商品
consuming items a subscriber subscribes
订户消费的商品
to a publisher and can issue a request
给发布者，并可以发出请求
for items as needed
用于所需的物品
this request mechanism provides the
该请求机制提供了
subscriber with back pressure since it
订户具有背压，因为它
is in control of the maximum number of
控制最大数量
items that may be sent to it as we just
可能像我们刚发送给它的项目
seen in the last slide
在上一张幻灯片中看到
HTTP request body is provided through a
HTTP请求主体是通过
body publisher by
正文发布者
publisher is a subtype of flow publisher
发布者是流发布者的子类型
that publishes httprequest body as bytes
将httprequest主体发布为字节
the HTTP requests by the publishers
发布者的HTTP请求
class provides a collection of factoring
类提供了分解的集合
methods for creating publishers for most
大多数创建发布者的方法
common use cases for example publishing
常见用例，例如发布
request body from a string are
来自字符串的请求正文是
publishing request body from the file
从文件发布请求正文
and more besides similarly under
还有更多类似的情况
receiving side the HTTP response body
接收方HTTP响应主体
subscriber is a subtype of java.util
Subscriber是java.util的子类型
concurrent flow subscriber it is a
并发流订阅者
subscriber of response body bytes again
响应主体字节的订阅者再次
there's a class body subscribers that
有一个班级订户
provides a number of factory methods for
提供了许多工厂方法
creating body subscribers for most
为大多数人创建机构订户
common use cases for example converting
常见用例，例如转换
response body bytes into a string or
响应正文字节转换为字符串或
streaming the bytes to a file custom
将字节流传输到文件自定义
publishers and subscribers can be
发布者和订阅者可以是
written by implementing the body
通过执行身体写
publisher and body subscriber interfaces
发布者和主体订户接口
to summarize the standard HTTP client
总结标准的HTTP客户端
added in java 11 is a replacement for
Java 11中添加的是对
performing HTTP access through the URL
通过URL执行HTTP访问
connection api which as we've seen is
我们已经看到的连接API
now more than twenty years old the HTTP
现在已有二十多年的HTTP
client api was incubated in jdk 9
客户api在jdk 9中孵育
refreshed in jdk 10 and finally
在jdk 10中刷新，最后
standardized in Java 11 code using the
使用Java 11代码标准化
incubating version of the API will need
需要孵化版本的API
to be updated for Java 11 minimally the
至少要针对Java 11进行更新
import statements will need to reflect a
导入声明将需要反映
new standard package name the HTTP
新的标准包名称HTTP
client API uses more modern language
客户端API使用更现代的语言
features like generics and lambda as
像泛型和lambda这样的功能
well as more modern platform api is like
以及更现代的平台api就像
compatible future and reactive reactive
兼容未来和反应性
streams interfaces you can download Java
您可以下载Java的流接口
now 11 now at this URL please join us at
现在11现在在此URL处，请加入我们
open JDK follow us on Twitter at open
打开JDK在Twitter上关注我们
JDK or hashtag Java 11 my own twitter
JDK或主题标签Java 11我自己的Twitter
handle is at checker 999 oracle is the
句柄在检查器999 oracle是
stuartt of java providing a large amount
Java的stuartt提供了大量
of development engineering funding for
的开发工程资金
the Java SE platform and open JDK Oracle
Java SE平台并打开Oracle JDK
provides leading class premier support
提供一流的总理支持
for a low cost that's easy to purchase
易于购买的低成本
with simple pricing tiers thank you for
具有简单的定价等级谢谢
watching
观看
[Music]
[音乐]